# **Muhammad Haris**

A self-motivated, creative, and a proven team player, I have six months of intern experience in variety of roles and responsibilities is Front End Development building and managing small- and large-scale web applications. I have hands on experience working with technologies React JS, React Bootstrap, CSS 3, HTML 5, Bootstrap4 and extensive experience consuming REST Web Api.

## **Work Experience**

## **Borialas Enterprises**

July 2022 - Dec 2022

6 months

Mern stack

I worked for the Borialas enterprise, making many projects such as landing pages, ecommerce pages, and other web designes for the existing websites, using the Reactjs and Nextjs framworks mainly, and also include other techs

Other techs include the tailwind css, shaden, custom css, supabase, Prisma, Nodejs, Airtable etc.

## **Venux Byte**

Mar 2023 - Aug 2023

- I worked remotely for them as a frontend developer This company provides, legal services, other non-skilled services.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to develop and implement web applications.
- It includes tech like React Bootstrap, React JS, Angular Js, tailwind css, Htm15, CSS3, Bootstrap 4.

#### **Smash Code**

Sep 2023 - Present...

I worked on many projects for this company mainly is Lens protocol projects, and frontend projects like making dashboards ecommerce and jobboard.

technology. React Bootstrap, React JS, Nextjs, Lens Protocol, Blockchain, tailwind css, Htm15, CSS3, Bootstrap 4.

## **Educational Background**

#### **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science**

University of Swabi ( Aug 2017 - Aug 2021 ) GPA 3.22 out of 4.00.

#### Contact

Islamabad Street 13A, E11/4 +92 3159980080 developerofficials.1@gmail.com www.Myportfolio.com

#### Skills

React js fully handed

#### Technical Skills

Making designs from figma Cloning websites Team developement Learning new techs easily

### **Projects: (with links)**

- Crypto-z
- Dashboard Project
- <u>Encounters</u> and many more ...

### Languages

- English (Fluent)
- Urdu (Fluent)
- Pushto (Proficient)

### **Certification/Short Courses**

- PFTP Internship
- > Eziline internship

## **Additional Information**

- Served as Team Lead in the company's projects.
- Made many projects by myself